Privacy Policy and Terms of Service
===================================

Last updated on Oct 31, 2024

Privacy Policy
--------------

This policy describes the ways we collect, store, use and protect your personal information. You accepted this policy when you signed up for our Service. We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it. Should a revision prove unacceptable to you, please contact us at support@clean.email.

Our Commitment To Privacy
-------------------------

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. It represents our good-faith efforts to ensure your privacy and provide you with a great service.

The Information We Collect
--------------------------

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Clean Email. The types of personal information collected includes but is not limited to:

* Email address
* For third party mail providers (e.g., Gmail, Outlook, Yahoo, AOL) we may have to store authorization credentials and related information for other sites. We will make it clear that we are requesting this information before you provide it and you can contact to have it removed.
* Data you give us permission to access (e.g., your Emails, Profile)

We only access the envelope and header information associated with your emails. The actual bodies of your emails are never downloaded or accessed within our computer systems.

The Way We Use Information
--------------------------

We use your email address to communicate with you and to authenticate with 3rd party products integrated with our system. We will never sell or rent your email address or ANY personally identifiable or even aggregated information to another company.

For diagnostic purposes, our engineers may have access to private data (e.g., to fix a problem with the service). Before gaining such access, however, they must get management approval, and we are committed to maintaining the privacy of that data. Regardless, we will not read the bodies of your email messages (we may have to look at the envelopes (To/From/Subject/Date) as part of our diagnosis, but we ignore the bodies of messages).

We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website.

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies in order to track authentication and other session information. These cookies are not shared with other sites and are not related to any marketing activities.

All personally identifiable information gathered can be disclosed to judicial or other government agencies subject to warrants, subpoenas or other governmental orders. But absent a legal compulsion, we will not divulge your information.

Finally, we do not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above.

Additional Limits on Use of Your Google User Data
-------------------------------------------------

Notwithstanding anything else in this Privacy Policy, if you provide Clean Email access to your Google data, Clean Email’s use of that data will be subject to these additional restrictions:

* Clean Email will only use access to read or control Gmail message metadata (including information about attachments), headers to provide a web service that allows users to process (delete/move/archive) emails and will not transfer this Gmail data to others unless doing so is necessary to provide and improve these features, comply with applicable law, or as part of a merger, acquisition, or sale of assets.
* Clean Email will not use this Gmail data for serving advertisements.
* Clean Email will not allow humans to read this data unless we have your affirmative agreement for specific messages, doing so is necessary for security purposes such as investigating abuse, to comply with applicable law, or for Clean Email’s internal operations and even then only when the data have been aggregated and anonymized.
* Clean Email use of information received from Google APIs will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy#additional_requirements_for_specific_api_scopes), including the Limited Use requirements.

Our Commitment To Data Security
-------------------------------

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

All payments and payment information on our site is handled through FastSpring which is fully PCI DSS compliant. PCI DSS is the global standard for safeguarding financial transaction data. Payments for iOS mobile apps are charged to your "iTunes Account" at confirmation of purchase. No customer financial information is ever stored within our computer systems.

Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
------------------------------------

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

Who Owns Your Data?
-------------------

You own the data associated with your account. And, at any time, you can securely remove your data from our servers by using a feature in the application or contacting our support and requesting such a deletion. This will be true even during a corporate merger or a corporate bankruptcy.

Data Retention
--------------

When you cancel your membership, your account will remain active for the time your subscription was paid for unless otherwise requested. All cancelled subscriptions are automatically deactivated at the end of the paid period and they will revert to free accounts status.

All the data indexed for your email is automatically deleted from our servers 45 days after your last login to the service as long as there is no active subscription running.

If for any reason, we decide to close Clean Email, all users will be contacted by email and their account information will be securely deleted from our servers in a timely manner.

Terms of Service
----------------

### Acceptance of the Terms of Use

Welcome to the website of Clean Email. ("Company", "we" or "us"). The following terms and conditions (together with any documents referred to in them) (collectively, these "Terms of Use") apply to your use of Clean Email web or mobile apps, including any content, functionality and services offered on or through Clean Email (the "Website").

Please read the Terms of Use carefully before you start to use the site. By using the Website, you accept and agree to be bound and abide by these Terms of Use and our Privacy Notice, found at https://clean.email/privacy, incorporated here by reference. If you do not want to agree to these Terms of Use or the Privacy Notice, you must exit the Website.

### Changes to the Terms of Use

We may revise and update these Terms of Use from time to time in our sole discretion. You are expected to check this page from time to time to take notice of any changes we made, as they are binding on you. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of revised Terms of Use means that you accept and agree to the changes.

### Accessing the Website and Account Security

By using this Website, you represent and warrant that you are 18 years or older.

We reserve the right to withdraw or amend this Website, and any service or material we provide on the Website, in our sole discretion without notice. We will not be liable if for any reason all or any part of the Website is unavailable at any time or for any period. From time to time, we may restrict access to some parts of the Website, or the entire Website, to users, including registered users.

You are responsible for making all arrangements necessary for you to have access to the Website.

You are responsible for ensuring that all persons who access the Website through your internet connection are aware of these Terms of Use, and that they comply with them.

To access the Website or some of the resources it offers, you may be asked to provide certain registration details or other information. It is a condition of your use of the Website that all the information you provide on the Website is correct, current and complete.

If you choose, or you are provided with, a user name, password or any other piece of information as part of our security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential, and you must not disclose it to any third party. You agree to immediately notify Company of any unauthorized use of your user name or password or any other breach of security. You also agree to ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. You should use particular caution when accessing your account from a public or shared computer so that others are not able to view or record your password or other personal information.

We have the right to disable any user identification code or password, whether chosen by you or provided by us, at any time in our sole discretion for any or no reason, including, if in our opinion, you have failed to comply with any provision of these Terms of Use.

### Intellectual Property Rights

The Website and its entire contents, features and functionality (including but not limited to all information, software, text, displays, images, video and audio, and the design, selection and arrangement thereof), are owned by the Company, its licensors or other providers of such material and are protected by United States and international copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret and other intellectual property or proprietary rights laws.

You are permitted to use the Website for non-commercial use only. You must not copy, modify, create derivative works of, publicly display, publicly perform, republish, download, store or transmit any of the material on our site, except to:

* Store copies of such materials temporarily in RAM.
* Store files that are automatically cached by your Web browser for display enhancement purposes.
* Print a reasonable number of pages of the Website for a permitted use.

You must not:

* Modify copies of any materials from this site.
* Delete or alter any copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights notices from copies of materials from this site.
* You must not reproduce, sell or exploit for any commercial purposes any part of the Website, access to the Website or use of the Website or any services or materials available through the Website.

If you print, copy, modify, download or otherwise use any part of the Website in breach of the Terms of Use, your right to use the Website will cease immediately and you must, at our option, return or destroy any copies of the materials you have made. No right, title or interest in or to the Website or any content on the site is transferred to you, and all rights not expressly granted are reserved by the Company. Any use of the Website not expressly permitted by these Terms of Use is a breach of these Terms of Use and may violate copyright, trademark and other laws.

### Company Trademarks

The Company name, and all related names, logos, product and service names, designs and slogans are trademarks of the Company or its affiliates or licensors. You must not use such marks without the prior written permission of the Company. All other names, brands and marks are used for identification purposes only and are the trademarks of their respective owners.

### Prohibited Uses

You may use the Website only for lawful purposes and in accordance with these Terms of Use. You agree not to use the Website:

In any way that violates any applicable federal, state, local and international law or regulation (including, without limitation, any laws regarding the export of data or software to and from the US or other countries).

To engage in any other conduct that restricts or inhibits anyone's use or enjoyment of the Website, or which, as determined by us, may harm the Company or users of the Website or expose them to liability.

Additionally, you agree not to:

* Use the Website in any manner that could disable, overburden, damage, or impair the site or interfere with any other party's use of the Website, including their ability to engage in real time activities through the Website.
* Use any robot, spider or other automatic device, process or means to access the Website for any purpose, including to monitor or copy any of the material on the Website.
* Use any manual process to monitor or copy any of the material on the Website or for any other unauthorized purpose without our prior written consent.
* Use any device, software or routine that interferes with the proper working of the Website.
* Introduce any viruses, trojan horses, worms, logic bombs or other material which is malicious or technologically harmful.
* Attempt to gain unauthorized access to, interfere with, damage or disrupt any parts of the Website, the server on which the Website is stored, or any server, computer or database connected to the Website.
* Attack the Website via a denial-of-service attack or a distributed denial-of-service attack.
* Otherwise attempt to interfere with the proper working of the Website.

### Reliance on Information Posted

The information presented on or through the Website is made available solely for general information purposes. We do not warrant the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of this information. Any reliance you place on such information is strictly at your own risk. We disclaim all liability and responsibility arising from any reliance placed on such materials by you or any other visitor to the Website, or by anyone who may be informed of any of its contents.

### Changes to the Website

We may update the Website from time to time, but its content is not necessarily complete or up-to-date. Any of the material on the Website may be out of date at any given time, and we are under no obligation to update such material. We may change the Website at any time with or without notice. We may suspend access to the Website, or close it indefinitely.

### Information About You and Your Visits to the Website

All information we collect on this Website is subject to our Privacy Notice . By using the Website, you consent to all actions taken by us with respect to your information in compliance with the Privacy Policy. You represent and warrant that all data provided by you is accurate.

### Linking to the Website

You may link to our homepage, provided you do so in a way that is fair and legal and does not damage our reputation or take advantage of it, but you must not establish a link in such a way as to suggest any form of association, approval or endorsement on our part where none exists.

You must not establish a link from any website that is not owned by you.

The Website must not be framed on any other site, nor may you create a link to any part of the Website other than the homepage.

You agree to cooperate with us in causing any unauthorized framing or linking immediately to cease. We reserve the right to withdraw linking permission without notice.

### Links from the Website

If the Website contains links to other sites and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your convenience only. This includes links contained in advertisements, including sponsored links. We have no control over the contents of those sites or resources, and accept no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them. If you decide to access any of the third party websites linked to this Website, you do so entirely at your own risk and subject to the terms and conditions of use for such websites.

### Warranty Disclaimer

Save to the extent required by applicable law, Clean Email does not accept any fiduciary duty to you. You access and use the Website and the Services is at your own risk.

The Website and Services are made available to you “as is” and “as available”, without warranty of any kind, for your information and personal use only (except as expressly permitted otherwise by Clean Email). To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, Clean Email, its officers, directors, employees, and agents disclaim all warranties, express or implied, in connection with the Website, the Services and their content, including the Content, and your use thereof. Clean Email makes no warranties or representations regarding the accuracy, currency, availability, suitability or completeness of the content available on the Site and through the Services, and to the maximum extent permitted under applicable law, Clean Email disclaims all warranties that the Website and Services are free from viruses or other harmful components, and the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title, and non-infringement. Clean Email does not make any warranty (i) that the Website and Services shall meet your requirements or expectations, (ii) that the Website and Services shall be available on an uninterrupted, timely, secure or error-free basis, (iii) that the results that may be obtained from the use of the Website and Services shall be accurate and reliable, and (iv) regarding the quality of the Website and the Services. In particular (without being exhaustive), Clean Email assumes no liability or responsibility for any:

* errors, mistakes, or inaccuracies of content (including Content),
* personal injury or property damage, of any nature whatsoever, resulting from your access to and use of our Website and Services,
* any unauthorized access to or use of our servers and/or any content, including Content, personal information and/or financial information, stored therein,
* any interruption or cessation of transmission to or from our Website or Services,
* any bugs, viruses, trojan horses, or the like which may be transmitted to or through our Website or Services through the actions of any third party, including users, and/or
* any errors or omissions in any content or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any content, including Content.

Clean Email does not warrant, endorse, recommend, guarantee, or assume responsibility for any product or services advertised or offered by a third party through the Website, the Services or any hyperlinked website or featured in any user submission or other advertising, and Clean Email will not be a party to or in any way be responsible for monitoring any transaction between you and third-party providers of products or services.

The above disclaimer does not affect legal rights which cannot be excluded under applicable law.

### Limitation of Liability

To the maximum extent permitted under applicable law, Clean Email hereby excludes its, its affiliates’, its officers’, directors’, employees’, and agents’ liability to you and any third parties for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, punitive, or consequential damages whatsoever resulting from (your access to and use of) the Website, the Services and their content (including the Content), including (without being limitative) loss of data, loss of revenue or profit, loss of anticipated savings, reputational damage.

Clean Email in particular (without being limitative) does not accept any liability resulting from any:

* errors, mistakes, or inaccuracies of content (including Content),
* personal injury or property damage, of any nature whatsoever, resulting from your access to and use of our Website and/or Services,
* any unauthorized access to or use of our secure servers and/or any content (including Content), personal information and/or financial information stored therein,
* any interruption or cessation of transmission to or from our Website or Servers,
* any bugs, viruses, Trojan horses, or the like, which may be transmitted to or through our Website and Services by any third party (including users), and/or
* any errors or omissions in any content or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of your use of any content (including Content).
* in general, your access to, display of, submission of any Content on, your reliance on, or use of the Website or the Services, or resulting from the delay or inability to access, display or submit any Content on or use the Website or the Services.

### Indemnification

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Clean Email, its affiliates, officers, directors, employees, and agents, on a full indemnity basis and at Clean Email’s first request, from and against any and all claims, damages, obligations, losses, liabilities, costs or debt, fines, penalties and expenses (including but not limited to attorney's fees) arising from (i) your use of and access to the Website or Services in breach of the Agreement; (ii) your violation of any applicable law or any term of the Agreement; (iii) your violation of any third party right, including without limitation any copyright, property, or privacy right; or (iv) any claim that Contents you posted caused damage to a third party. This defense and indemnification obligation will survive the Agreement and your use of the Services. Clean Email reserves the right to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter subject to indemnification by you hereunder, in which event you will assist and cooperate with Clean Email in asserting any available defenses, at your expense.

### Governing Law and Jurisdiction

The laws of California, U.S.A., will apply to any disputes arising out of or relating to these terms or the Website. All claims arising out of or relating to these terms or the Website will be litigated exclusively in the federal or state courts of California, USA, and you and we consent to personal jurisdiction in those courts.

### Limitation on Time to File Claims

ANY CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM YOU MAY HAVE ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THESE TERMS OF USE OR THE WEBSITE MUST BE COMMENCED WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES, OTHERWISE, SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM IS PERMANENTLY BARRED.

### Waiver and Severability

No waiver of these Terms of Use by the Company shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or any other term or condition, and any failure of the Company to assert a right or provision under these Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.

If any provision of these Terms of Use is held by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, illegal or unenforceable for any reason, such provision shall be eliminated or limited to the minimum extent such that the remaining provisions of the Terms of Use will continue in full force and effect.

### Entire Agreement

The Terms of Use and our Privacy Notice constitute the sole and entire agreement between you and Clean Email with respect to the Website and supersede all prior and contemporaneous understandings, agreements, representations and warranties, both written and oral, with respect to the Website.

### Your Comments and Concerns

This website is operated by Clean Email

All other feedback, comments, requests for technical support and other communications relating to the Website should be directed to our support team.

Subscription Fees
-----------------

You shall pay for all subscription fees, and hereby authorize Clean Email (and its payment processors) to debit your bank account or charge your credit card. **You agree that all subscription plans are recurring and will be renewed automatically.**

Cancellation Policy
-------------------

You acknowledge that all subscription fees are charged automatically on a recurring basis **until you cancel your subscription (both month-to-month and annual plans).**

You have the right to cancel your subscription at any time by using a link to manage the subscription from the payment confirmation email sent to you after the purchase or by informing us about your decision by email at support@clean.email at least 2 business days before your subscription renewal date. Please keep in mind that **you are solely responsible for properly canceling your account.** Make sure you tell us your name and email used for the purchase. We will not be able to find your subscription if we don't have the correct details. Your access to the service will still be available until the end of the period you paid for.

Refunds
-------

Clean Email offers a free limited trial to anyone who wants to check out the service before committing to a paid subscription.

For clients who purchased the subscription without using the trial Clean Email can issue a refund for the service within 30 days of the original purchase date of the product under certain conditions:

* You are unable to access the service (your email service is not supported)
* You asked for a refund within 7 days of your purchase without using the service. This also applies to rebills (e.g.: you have been billed but did not use the service)

**The chosen subscription is billed in advance on a monthly or annual basis and is non-refundable; no refunds will be issued unless otherwise required by law**. Clean Email does not offer prorated refunds for canceled subscription plans. **All subscription plans are recurring** and will be automatically renewed after the end of each paid subscription period. This includes both month-to-month and annual plans.

Clean Email does not provide refunds or credits for any term prepaid by you and you will not receive any refund for any unused days of any periodic subscription term unless otherwise required by law. In order to treat everyone equally, no exceptions will be made.

To avoid abuses of the service no refunds will be given to repeated purchases (users who purchased in the past and canceled) and for rebills where a proper cancellation request was not made at least 2 business days before the charge.

We recommend contacting us for assistance if you experience any issues receiving or using our service.

Clean Email’s Refund Policy for Annual Plans
--------------------------------------------

Clean Email is committed to the success of our customers, but through experience we have found that users have varying requirements, capabilities, and limitations with regard to the types of devices and software they can use, the way their local network is configured, the speed of their internet connection, etc.

These issues may impact a customer’s ability to use Clean Email as it is intended.

Accordingly, Clean Email offers a Free Limited Trial, and is happy to extend the trial limit for users who need to better evaluate our services and its compatibility with their specific needs.

Clean Email also offers Month-to-Month Subscription Plans to allow customers to upgrade, downgrade, and cancel the subscription plan at any time without penalty. We recommend this option for most customers, especially those who do not have full certainty or control over their technology environment.

Finally, Clean Email offers an Annual Subscription Plan at a significant discount. **We recommend this plan for customers who are certain that Clean Email is compatible with their needs**. It is your responsibility to evaluate Clean Email, including its features, limitations, and system requirements before selecting the Annual Plan.

If you are not certain that Clean Email is a fit for your use case, then you should not choose the Annual Plan.

**Clean Email does not provide refunds to Annual Plans customers** on the basis of customers not understanding of the system requirements, or the presence of compatibility issues, including inadequate internet speed or consistency, or incompatible devices, operating systems, or browser software versions.

If you choose the Annual Plan, you are entering into a one-year subscription contract that expires 12 months after you sign up. You are responsible for paying for the entire subscription term. If you decide to cancel your subscription before the subscription term, then you will still be billed for the remaining months of your subscription, and you will still have access to the benefits of the service until the end of the term.

Contact us
----------

If you have any questions about our policies, please contact us by email at support@clean.email

5 Billion

emails cleaned yearly

10 Years

in business

**Excellent 4.7** out of 5

**Our rating 4.5** out of 5

**4.4 •** 2.7K Ratings

Features

Resources

How-to Guides

Email Detox

Inbox Zero

Compare

Platforms

Company

Headquartered in Los Angeles, California. Made by a remote team from all over the world.

© 2015-2024 Clean Email, LLC. All Rights Reserved.

[Privacy policy](https://clean.email/privacy)•[Terms of Service](#)•[Contact us](https://clean.email/support)•[Vulnerability Disclosure Program](https://clean.email/vdp)

  English
